So you're sure the last time
you saw her was last night.
Yeah.
Sarge.
We thought you might want to hear this.
It's just that Claudia
didn't show up for work.
wasn't answering her phone.
so I checked on her.
found her here. overdosed.
And that you weren't the
last one to see her.
No. I let Louie in around
1:00. then I took off.
Louie? Franklin Saint's auntie?
Yeah.
Hey. baby.
Hmm? Mm...
I didn't want to leave
without talking to you.
Just... I'm fine. baby.
- I just need to rest. Go.
- Mm-hmm.
Maybe I should stay home today.
Mm-mm. Jerome. I'm for real.
Just go. I just need to sleep.
All right. baby. I'll see you tonight.
Why are we waiting?
We should take her in.
That's why.
Let's get her.
Los Angeles Police Department.
LAPD. Open up.
Look. I already told you
that shit was clean.
Just me and Fatback. in and out.
You sure nobody saw you?
Franklin. how the fuck
am I supposed to be sure
about some shit like that?
I ain't been picked up yet.
so why you sweating me?
'Cause Andre came at me last night.
Seems to have in his head
that we a problem that
need to be dealt with.
Well. ain't Andre had that
in his head for a while now?
Not like this.
They coming for us. man.
Our people. our money.
We got to be smarter. protect ourselves.
Come on.
What's up. y'all?
We straight?
Depends. You got the cash?
Hold up.
What's your plan?
My plan? What you mean. my plan?
I'm-a sell that rock.
When it's gone. buy some more.
- then I'm gonna sell that. too.
- And expand?
Talking about staying
out of your territory.
- I know what's what.
- You better make sure
your crew know that shit. too. then.
Hey.
Remember back at Foshay.
that food fight that turned into a riot?
Oh. yeah. That shit was crazy.
- Yeah.
- The fire alarms ringing.
Shit. a couple motherfuckers
went after their teachers
with their trays.
Mm. Knocked that old
lunch lady out cold.
- That lunch lady. Damn.
- You know.
a few of us. we knew
to stay out the mess.
Not to go after each
other or the teachers.
Shit. I hopped that
fence and I was gone.
Yeah.
You know...
... this shit?
We stay out the mess.
Yeah. I'm with you.
Holler when you want some more.
Fo sho.
That's cute.
He really run away from that fight?
Nah.
He was the one that knocked
out the lunch lady.
Fuck you. Andre!
I want my goddamn lawyer
right fucking now!
We have her at the scene. but
she lied about the timeline.
All circumstantial.
The last thing we need is to put an OD
on the board as a murder.
Why don't you let it rest
until the ME report comes in?
Because that's Franklin Saint's auntie.
The kid who beat the murder
rap a couple months ago?
Look. we got her 24 hours. right?
Let me go in there and sweat her.
shake out some evidence.
see if I can get something
to leverage her with.
We do have to go to court today.
All right. Sergeant.
Go in it.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
- Hey.
- They counter?
Came back with no contingencies.
and 50.000 above asking.
50? You serious?
Yeah. They claim to have another offer.
I'll need to move additional funds over
if we're gonna counter.
I can pull what we need from
the accounts in Jersey.
Uh. if we decide to up our offer.
I'll just move cash to
the escrow account.
Why? What's wrong with
our offshore accounts
- all of a sudden?
- You know. right now.
I want to keep all our
real estate holdings clear
of any money Reed Thompson knows about.
Just to be safe.
Uh...
Uh. give me a minute. okay?
Hey. it's Yuda. Avi's here.
You can come up to the house.
Good. All right. I'm on my way.
I got to run.
- Franklin...
- Tell me something.
you think they really got another offer?
Uh. I have no idea. It's possible.
Hmm. All right. let me think on it.
I love you.
Listen to me. Louie.
We got a witness put you at the scene.
And I also know you and
Claudia had a fight
a while back. put her in the hospital.
That's motive.
Tell me what happened now.
and maybe I can help you.
You full of shit.
The window in the bathroom
didn't have the shades down.
It faces the building in the back.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Cooperation at this stage means a lot.
But once I file
witnesses. hard evidence?
Ain't a damn thing I can do.
Franklin!
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Avi.
Everything okay?
Everything's peachy.
Just a little preoccupied. that's all.
So what's up?
I need your advice on something.
Having some issues on my cash flow.
What. those rocks of yours not selling?
Actually. they moving better than ever.
Problem is...
I don't know what to do with my money.
The best kind of problems.
Yeah.
- But problems just the same.
- Hmm.
A while back. you was telling me
- about offshore banking.
- Hmm.
That something you could
still help me with?
Ah. well. That depends.
How much money we talking about?
Six inch open-bolt
- submachine gun.
- How many rounds per minute?
950.
Why don't you...
let me talk to some of my contacts?
See what I can do.
You like?
Hell. no.
You was gonna shoot me with
that. first time we met.
Ah. I was never gonna shoot you.
I was testing you.
There's a big difference.
Sure you're okay. Avi?
The longer you live.
the more mistakes you make.
And eventually. if you're not careful...
... they catch up with you.
What mistakes?
No matter.
Never get too greedy. Franklin.
The minute you do that...
they found your weakness.
You lost your advantage.
Yuda. show our. uh. young friends out.
And give Leon here an extra Uzi
with a couple of mags.
So... you'll see why the Israelis make
the best weapons.
Here you go. man. Enjoy.
Hell. yeah.
Keep the advantage. my friend.
¿Hola?
Yo soy Gustavo.
Este es Reed.
Oh. es típico.
¿Eh?
Hello?
Hello. is anybody there? I got to use
the goddamn bathroom!
Hello?!
Hello?
Fuck!
Come on. I got to pee!
I know you fucking see me!
Hey. Louie.
Got you some Jim Dandy's.
Sweet bread rolls and peppers.
Louie.
Hey...
Hey. Louie.
Hey. baby.
What...?
Oh. shit!
- Shit. Damn!
- Yeah. yeah.
All right.
- Hey. let me get a turn. bruh.
- Hey. in a minute.
- What about me?
- Man. come on.
I don't need shit. y'all
gon' have to get your own.
Oh. come on. sharing is caring.
- Shit! Fuck. you all right?
- Oh!
Yeah. I'm good.
Hey. Leon. man.
- Hey.
- Hey. hey.
Hell. no. man. What I told
your little ass. man?
Get your ass out of here.
Look. I know what y'all
said. a'ight? But...
Man. I really want this
shit. man. I can help.
- What can you do?
- More than you.
- white boy.
- Oh.
I'm a soldier.
Fuck. a toy soldier.
Huh. yeah. keep talking that
shit. Fatboy. see what happen.
- Oh...
- Oh. shit. You gon' take
- that shit from him?
- No. no. fuck that.
I'm about to tell your
little ass what's up.
- Come on.
- Let's go. I ain't scared of you.
Come on. come on.
- Oh. I don't know. he's fast.
- I'm right here.
- What's up? Can't hit...
- Yeah... No. fuck.
- ... what you can't see. huh?
- Fuck that. Come on. come here.
- Yeah.
- All right. bitch. Now. yeah.
You gonna show off?
Well. let's see if your little ass
- can dodge a fucking bullet.
- Whoa.
Hey. Fatback. hold on. Hold up.
You know. we don't bring
no punks into this shit.
So whatever we say.
you fucking do it.
No questions.
You understand?
Hey. man. whatever the
fuck you want. a'ight?
I'm with it.
All right. get the fuck out of here.
Bitch-ass nigga.
- Better run. bitch.
- Fuck you.
Yeah. get your bitch ass out of here.
Man. I should've shot his ass.
Hey. that little nigga
got heart. though.
All right.
- Let's get this next light over here.
- Hell yeah. let's do it.
- Eyes closed? All right.
- Eyes closed. fuck it.
I apologize.
Had a lot of people to talk to.
Got a chance to talk to
more of Claudia's people.
I heard some pretty disturbing things.
Didn't realize her reputation.
Tricking out young girls.
breaking them down.
throwing them out.
She used them.
Probably used you. too.
You were just a young girl. right?
From Louisiana?
Man. I bet you she messed
with your head for years.
I've seen plenty like her.
Predators.
Look... nobody is gonna blame you
for going after someone who's abusive.
Someone you loved.
who toyed with you.
who liked making you feel like shit.
Sergeant.
Time's up. Andre. Her lawyer's here.
Clock's on. You got two minutes.
All right. here it is.
You're exhausted. right?
So let's just end this here and now.
We got opportunity.
Santos clocking your arrival.
leaving you alone with her.
We got evidence.
Your prints are in the house.
on the syringe she used to shoot up.
all over the bathtub. We got motive.
I read the hospital report
when you beat Claudia.
'cause that wasn't a fight.
You nearly killed her.
And that's a lot of bad blood.
And. finally. a witness.
An elderly woman. Mrs. Norman.
in the building across the way
has a view into the bathroom.
You didn't put the shades down.
She saw you exchange words.
You push her head under.
The struggle.
And then she was gone.
You a lying piece of shit.
A fucking witness.
Bring that bitch in here.
Ms. Motherfucking Norman.
bring her in here.
Louie. Louie. we can
figure this out together.
Oh. no. no. no! Bring that bitch
in here right motherfucking now!
I want my fucking lawyer!
Left. please.
Did you okay this?
Having a sergeant play detective?
Andre was just checking a few things out
while Aviles and I were in court.
Wright. you get anything?
No. sir.
But like I told you before.
this family is tied into...
We're up to our necks in
this summer games bullshit.
I don't need you off your watch.
Next time. you clear this
kind of shit with me.
Yes. sir.
You okay. baby? Hm?
- I just want to go home.
- Mm.
Mm.
Okay.
Yeah?
You got a minute?
- Hey.
Okay. s-so we did the drop in-in Mexico
a couple days back.
Teddy had to tell this
guy that I was DEA.
It's a long fucking story.
Rigo Vasco knew. He knew I was DEA.
- Jesus Christ.
- Someone's talking.
I don't know if it's someone in
the El Paso office. or if...
I don't... Somehow he has
access to the undercover files.
I don't fucking know.
- Tony. Tony.
- Okay.
You've got to be really
careful with this.
You start beating the bush now.
it points right back at me.
Hold on. you want to stay in.
They think I'm clean.
and you see how much I'm getting.
This guy Rigo. he supposedly reports
directly back to Matta-Ballesteros.
Why tell me all this if you
want me to fucking sit on it?
I'm not. I'm not saying that.
Start looking. but just do it quietly.
Contact anybody that you have undercover
and get them a warning.
Also.
I think Teddy's gonna reroute
the coke through Lucia's farm.
so I'm finally gonna get those fuckers.
I'd tell you to be careful.
but I know you'd just make fun of me.
This is a gift.
Don't waste it.
- I got to get back.
- Yeah.
Mr. Wright. how you doing?
Boy. what the hell you doing here?
I was just wondering if Melody was home.
- She in?
- What?
If Mel... Hey.
How you doing?
What's up?
Wanted to see if you wanted
to go to Baskin-Robbins.
Don't do this here. boy.
My treat.
Not tonight. Franklin.
No problem.
Oh.
Got this for you.
She don't want it.
Have a nice night. sir.
D-Dad. Dad.
Hey. Hey. Hey. hey.
Evening. Andre.
Franklin.
Everything all right?
Fine.
Night. Mel.
- Teddy.
- Whoa. whoa.
It's just me.
What the...
What the fuck are you doing here?
You're a hard man to get ahold of.
- The recent airdrops...
- Have been disrupted.
- I know.
- Not just diverted or delayed.
but shot down. Weapons taken
and used against the Contras.
Have you even read the
latest dispatches?
This week... uh. hasn't been...
great.
Had to take Matt home. so...
The Sandinistas have found a way
to track our movements out of Honduras.
We need to find another way.
Okay.
I'll figure it out.
I already did a little looking into it.
The problem... is the entry point.
Costa Rica. A private airstrip.
You'll be able to make your flight paths
more unpredictable and
use ground transports.
And the Costa Rican government?
Can't know anything about it. of course.
But we may have some support there.
From who?
A former operative in
the Talamanca region.
A smuggler.
He has an airstrip. but...
it's a matter of establishing
contact and he's a bit...
off the grid.
Okay.
You got. uh. the details for me?
For us.
I'm here to help... quietly.
I'm to brief you with the option
of coordinating and aiding.
Y-You're gonna stay here and help me?
When you came to me in D.C..
sent me to Havemeyer.
you put me in the middle of this.
Oh...
yeah. so I guess...
that means that you're
reporting back to them.
You threatened to make noise. Teddy.
What did you think was gonna happen?
Operational reports out of Nicaragua
are fine; I do not want them knowing
- the identities of any of my assets here.
- Of course.
I won't jeopardize your people.
And...
I mean. you're okay?
- Doing this with me?
- You read about
the American journalist killed
in the La Penca bombing?
The Sandinistas are getting
the upper hand. Teddy.
This isn't about us.
Show me the. um...
- show me the airstrip.
- Okay. mm-hmm.
So he's in the mountainous region here.
Yeah.
Which gives us these options.
The cove in here...
Yeah. I know. Stern and
Aviles briefed me.
You gave it a shot.
I appreciate the initiative. Wright.
You'll make Sergeant II in no time.
Thanks for stopping by.
Thank you. sir.
But... something's happening
in my neighborhood.
There's more money on the streets.
more shootings. new drugs.
Something's changing in a big way.
You run it up the chain?
Lieutenant Todd?
Oh. yes. sir. But the
Lieutenant isn't that. um...
interested.
Well... it's admirable to live and work
in the community. Good on you. Wright.
Captain.
This is something new.
Okay? It-it's. it's called "rock."
And it's expanding
beyond my neighborhood
and moving up towards the Coliseum.
Chief Gates got that area locked down.
Oh. of course he does. but...
with the opening ceremonies
around the corner. I figured...
it should be brought to your attention.
What are you suggesting?
Here he come.
I hate this nigga. man.
Ease up.
Good to see you boys enjoying
this nice summer day.
Should be nice if you got the cash.
'Course I do. Lil' Lee.
I trust the count's right.
Think I'm gonna fuck around with y'all
the way that pure rock movin'?
So. you got my re-up or what?
Come on.
All right. so. we gonna do things
just a little different. Drew.
I'm gonna give you two birds. untouched.
You're gonna cook it
yourself. rock it yourself.
cut it yourself.
Little more sweat for a lot more cash.
You feel me?
- That a problem. little man?
- Just wondering why
y'all switching shit up already.
'Cause you can handle it.
That's why.
I mean. what. you got...
cornerboys. cookers.
No need for us to do the work
you can do for yourself. right?
You wanted trust?
Here it is.
All right. Saint.
See you soon.
Mm-hmm.
See y'all. boys.
I still think trusting that
motherfucker don't make no sense.
It makes perfect sense.
We getting hit. Lee.
Cops is on us.
Cornerboys getting sloppy.
More street business
means more problems.
Problems we don't need.
Nickel-and-diming rocks
eventually gonna get you busted.
Our advantage is pure product
at basement prices.
and that's where we gonna focus on.
From here on out.
we only want dealers who can buy kilos.
Identify 'em. send them to
Leon and Peaches to check out.
and Louie'll make the final decision.
But we're still moving rock. right?
For now...
we need the cash flow.
But eventually. the goal is to only deal
with a few high-level customers...
and serious fuckin' weight. huh?
Start thinking about
who you want to bring in. all right?
- Cool.
- All right. y'all.
All right. now. What's up. boy?
- See you. boy.
- A'ight. Unc.
- We're gonna get there.
- Thank you. man.
You feeling better?
Uh-huh.
My damn speakers.
- Time for you to go.
- I know what time it is.
Get on. nephew. Get on. now.
See y'all tomorrow.
Come on. baby.